

PERSONAL PROFILE

A Self-Taught Programmer & Flutter Development with handson experience in developing crossplatform iOS and Android Applications. Along with Dart & Flutter I have worked in python as a hobby which includes selenium web automation and scripting to automate the simple manual tasks related to Excel and website. In Past I have also worked as a Digital Marketer.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Hands-on Flutter experience
- Dart, JavaScript and Python experience
- GetX State & Route Management, Set State Management, Web API experience.
- Working knowledge of API including HTTP. Json Parsing.
- Good understanding of objectoriented programming
- Experience with third-party libraries and APIs.

OTHER SKILLS

- The ability to analyze & understand complex technical information.
- Excellent Communication Skills & Interpersonal Skills.
- Detail oriented & Attention to Detail.
- Excellent problem solver & Fast Learner.
- Digital Marketing Facebook Ads & Shopify Management.

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

SANOJ PRASAD

GET IN CONTACT

Mobile: +91-8802-394-281 Email: pimen07860@gmail.com

Address: Aali Vihar, Sarita Vihar, New Delhi - 110076

Github: github.com/Sanoj-Raja

WORK EXPERIENCE

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

Harold Electricals | April 2020 - March 2021

- Harold Electricals is a Lighting Decor Brand. They deal in all sort of lights like Chandelier, Wall Light, Hanging Light etc.
- I was working on Harold Electrical's E-Commerce Mobile App of the company to retain the customer & to become the first mover in the Lighting Decor Industry. This app is in the final phase of testing. This app has built using SET State – State Management, HTTP, JSON.
- I have also worked on a Lead Management app in their company. Lead Manager App provides lead from Facebook Ads to the backend sales team.
- Along with these apps I have worked on many Hobby Apps Project.

FACEBOOK ADS CAMPAIGN MANAGER

Harold Electricals | January 2020 - March 2020

- Harold Electricals is a Lighting Decor Brand. They deal in all sort of lights like Chandelier, Wall Light, Hanging Light etc.
- I was handling social media platforms such as Facebook & Instagram of the company and also running & handling Facebook & Instagram Ads Campaign & Graphic Designing.
- Handling Shopify Product Listing, Inventory Management, SEO & Content Writing. Online Reputation Management.

DIGITAL MARKETING EXECUTIVE

Migat Umrah | July 2019 - December 2019

- Miqat Umrah was a travel agency that provides hazz & umrah travel services. I was handling all the social media platforms of the company and also running & handling Facebook & Instagram Ads Campaign.
- Online Reputation Management, Graphic Designing, Video Editing.

EDUCATION HISTORY

CBSE BOARD

Passed Class 12th, In 2018 With 75%

CBSE BOARD

Passed Class 10th, In 2016 With 74%